alrighty my guy this is a crazy bug
thanks so much for agreeing to share it
thanks for having me all right I have
just because I'm here and I'm talking to
you I have my water I know you're really
into that dud there here it is right
here got my water H always wanted to
drink some water on this podcast dude
dreams dreams do come true um dude this
this bug was amazing and I so appreciate
you reaching out you know and and uh and
saying the kind things about like how
the pot has helped you get there and I
see you using as you know some of the
techniques we've talked about on the Pod
absolutely um so yeah I guess this is my
boy xss doctor take take it away man uh
tell us about this bug um so I was I I
started to hack on like a kind of a
large scope um Bounty that you know I
looked at it for a few days three days
really until I found a couple gadgets
the first Gadget I found uh on the main
site um it's kind of an e-commerce
platform um and uh I I was looking
through the the local storage parameters
and I just saw one that it just said was
just a JS file a remote JS file so I I
just replaced it with my own remote JS
file and it popped so that's Gadget
number one and not only did it pop but
it popped on every click of the
application wow dude so you were just
you were just casually scrolling through
the local storage entries yeah I was I
like I don't know sometimes I like to
look at local storage I look at window.
name like that's like kind of some of
the first things I do like anything that
I could mess with um so that was like
the first thing so I'm like okay if I
could set this local storage parameter I
have xss on every click and that's
pretty big so then I was like looked
around for a long time to see if there
was a way to arbitrarily set a local
storage parameter but there was not um
that's I feel like that's kind of rare I
don't know yeah it's pretty rare I mean
like normally you find that the other
way around right like you'll you'll find
the way to arbitrarily set a local
storage parameter and then you'll you'll
utilize that to get some exploit you
don't you you don't normally be like I
need to set a local storage parameter
and then like find a magical local story
set Gadget yeah it'll be ni that would
be cool but hey man you you you moved
Heaven and Earth to make this thing
happen so I'm not gonna put it Beyond
you I went crazy uh so then the the next
thing I was looking around and I found a
self xss on the site and that was in uh
when you're creating uh you can you can
post stuff you can post uh items to sell
and so when you're posting something to
sell in the description section um if
you put you know brackets or quotes it
would it would URL encode that but if
you do it in burp then or in kaido then
it then it will not it will it will fire
but it gives you a warning they know
about this it gives you a warning like
hey you've put Javascript in here if you
post this it will get taken out so it's
a self but but you can save the listing
for yourself for later so every time you
click on that listing the self xss
pops so you like create a draft and then
that draft has a self xss in it but if
you were to publish the draft the xss
would get stripped it's and it even like
has a thing that says that that's
hilarious that they allow that still I
don't understand um but so that was that
so I'm like okay great so I can set the
local storage parameter with that xss
self xss but now all I need is the
easiest thing to get an all of hacking
which is a login
csrf and so I'm like I'm done I even
started like texting my friends about
like I have this it's done yeah um and
then it turns out that this platform
like really really does not want you to
get a log in
csrf there's like 20 cookies oh set in
different in different pages when you
log in and if you if you just change the
session the session token it doesn't log
you in it like flips out and tells and
like alerts the
authorities so did that for like four
day five days maybe get dude you spent
four days trying to find a login SE surf
I tried to like mimic that flow oh no
and try to like set the right cookies
and like do all the right stuff and I I
still can't even figure out the flow to
be honest even after all that time oh my
gosh um so then I started looking at
subdomains and I actually did like Jay
haddix's entire thing to get all of the
you know and I spent like a week looking
at all the subdomain and I found
thankfully reflected xss on a sub do
sorry I saw a post message ref this via
post message on another
subdomain um thank God and so then I use
that to set the cookie for the main
domain uh so you just document.cookie
equals sorry or no no no I'm just trying
to put it all in my head so we've got
the graph here right so so you've got
the post message xss that's on the
subdomain so and because of that you can
set cookies for the the whole domain
right so then you you use the document
you use the post message xss to document
uh do cookie and set these cookies to
the specific path of the self
xss right that's right and then so you
essentially use it as a login C surf for
the main domain I used it as a log and
actually I still didn't really even
understand which cookies were wi so I
just I took all my cookies there was
like go like 12 to 13 cookies and I just
set all of them to my to my my attacker
cookies and even I got it's finally
worked after like the 12th cookie
um and then I I set it to a specific
path to the path of the self
xss and then I
redirected the the second uh window to
that so then it set the local storage
parameter and then I redirected it again
back to the main site where I then had
the xss wow okay so we do have a graph
on the screen for those of you that are
that are watching on YouTube um so the
the whole flow is this let me let me
repeat it back to you dude I also just
have to say crazy props for the amount
of like endurance and like I don't know
what's what's the word gaman is the word
in Japanese but like you just stuck to
it stuck to itness that you did to get
this um so you first step post message
xss on the subdomain then you use the
you get the xss then you use the Matan
bear trick to have yourself logged in as
the attacker only on that specific
endpoint that allows you to uh trigger
the self xss then now you you redirect
to that endpoint trigger the stored self
xss then that uh stored xss changes the
local storage entry that would would
create the persistent xss on every
single page and then now wherever the
victim clicks and they would never click
on your listing anyway because it's your
it's that the URL is your specific
listing so it's essentially as if they
were not logged in at all to the
attacker's account right they're just
logged into their own account correct
but the local storage is still shared
and so it pops xss on every single page
on the victim's account that is correct
that that's it's it was the greatest
moment of my life I mean I think I mean
I have kids but I think it was the
greatest moment of my life oh my god
dude what a what an amazing what an
amazing find and um yeah so you built
out a little lab for this as well so
thanks for that um we're actually going
to drop that lab and a little
explanation of the lab um to the
critical thinkers tier on Discord so um
we'll go ahead and cut it here and uh if
you're interested in seeing the rest of
it make sure you check out the critical
thinkers uh on
Discord thanks so much
d